Hello. My name is Miku Kanemura.
Can you see where I am now?
I'm here at Hida Kanayama Station, which means I'm in Gifu Prefecture.
The reason I'm here today is because I'm here for an art festival in Minami Hida.
That's right!
I'm going to visit the festival tomorrow.
but I'm here at Hida Kanayama station for the day before the festival.
I'm going to take a little walk with my camera
I'm going to take a little walk with my camera today to get motivated for art.
Let's go!
I always travel alone like this.
It looks a little lighter than usual.
I usually carry a bigger backpack.
I'm wearing it alone.
But this area is called
It's called “Golden Bone”.
It's been around for a long time.
There's a house called
It's like a remnant of a house.
I don't know what to call it.
It's an amazing townscape.
It's like one of the most beautiful spots in the city.
I've only been walking for about 5 minutes.
I can see the mountain right away.
Wow!
Ta-da!
Oh, wow.
That's pretty impressive.
I want to take a picture.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Okay!
I came to a charming road with a beautiful river color.
There seems to be a spot near here that I wanted to photograph the most.
I'd like to take a peek.
Is it around here or there? Can you see it?
Ta-da!
There are some bridges.
It's a little bit like a tin roof.
I'm going to do some shooting around here.
I'll set it up like this.
Once you get a good angle of view...
I recommend using this remote control.
Even if you go far away from the camera
Even if you go quite far, you can still get this signal.
With this, you can take pictures anytime, anywhere
Even if you are running, you can take a picture.
I'm holding the remote control with my right hand.
With this, I can auto-focus
And it's in focus.
But if you want to show the whole picture
I think it's easier to take a picture
I think it's easier to make a mistake if you set the f-stop a little higher.
This is a shot I just took.
In this case, I think I'd like to get a little closer to the subject.
I thought it would be nice to show the atmosphere of the city
This is how I did it.
A house that looks like something out of Ghibli
It's a zone for houses that look like they're in spring.
I'll check it out.
Just a little further.
Almost there.
That's a tomato.
Oh, that's good.
Like this.
Here we go.
Where's the reflection?
Yo!
Yes, yes, yes.
A little OK
I've been to the puke spa!
I'm so glad!
I've heard of it.
I'm sure you've all heard of it.
But this is my first time here.
I heard there is a gourmet restaurant
I heard there's some good food around here.
I'd like to go there.
I've been thinking about it.
I've been wondering about.
There is!
The restaurant I was wondering about.
Yoshimaan, isn't it?
Hida Beef Nigiri?
This is it!
I've always wanted to try this.
I'll have one of these three main dishes, please.
Yes, about 5,000 yen!
I got the Hida Beef Nigiri!
I'd like to take a picture of the guy who was looking at this.
OK!
I'll start with the red meat.
Bon appétit!
The taste of the meat is pretty strong!
This looks delicious!
I'll have some of that sauce.
I'm hungry.
I could go for at least one more plate.
I could go for at least one more plate, but I think I'll hold off since it's about dinner time.
I could go for at least one more plate, but it's late in the evening, so I'd like to hold off.
We've arrived at Gero Onsen Gassho Mura (Gero Onsen Gassho Village).
This is a place with Gassho style houses.
I've always wanted to visit.
When you come to this area, you want to see traditional houses like Shirakawa-go, don't you?
This is a place where you can see them near Gerongsaeng.
I'd like to go there right away.
This is it.
Let's go there.
Wow!
It's really a village!
Soba-udon!
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
There are soba and udon restaurants like this.
Oh, now...
There's also a place under construction like this.
On the top
Straw.
There is a man who is building a house with straw.
This is a photo spot.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
It's called “Forest Slide” and it's 100 yen per use.
I'm a little curious about the slide.
I never thought there would be a slide here!
Wow!
Yaaaah!
It's fun!
I feel 10 years younger.
Hey!
Hot, hot, hot!
We went to Sasahara-san
Here's dinner...
Oh, no...
Here's your snacks... thank you
They're wonderful! Thank you!
Bon appétit!
Cinlena!
It's like a terrine.
Bon appétit.
Delicious!
I didn't think
I didn't think I'd be able to travel on the Hinatazaka channel.
I love to travel.
That's exactly what I'm going to do. I'm going to take Mari Moumoto and the others with me.
I mean, I'm the head of the travel club.
I hope I can come again with the members.
It's a great place!
It's delicious.
Delicious?
I think the 19th of April will be the first show in Hyogo.
Yesterday, I was talking with Kono-chan and Nik-chan about what kind of concert it would be.
This time it's going to be magical.
I think something is going to happen this time.
We haven't rehearsed yet, so
I can't say for sure.
What I would like to do is
I hope something unexpected happens, because the hiragana time was really fun with fresh saccharists.
It's an opportunity for the whole group to come together.
I hope the magic will happen.
Please look forward to seeing what will happen.
We have four graduates this time,
We have a lot of gigs and tours coming up.
I wondered if I would be able to charm them all.
I was wondering if I would be able to charm them all, so I am very happy that they are taking the time to do so.
I am very happy and
And I'm sad.
That's how we ended the dinner.
I'm so sad that I missed you all today, but I'm glad we're done.
I've been too happy all day today!
Tomorrow I'm going to an art festival, so I'm going to sleep early to be ready for it!
See you tomorrow!
Good morning!
Day 2
We are here at the Minami Hita Art Discovery!
I hope I can show you the beauty of art.
I'm off.
It's just down the street from the information center.
It's just down the street from the information center, but I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to get there.
The work I wanted to see the most today was
Mr. Sakata's paintings displayed in the forest.
He is one year older than me.
I thought there might be something I could learn from him.
Mr. Sakata's works
Mr. Sakata's work was created through interaction with the local people.
I thought it would be good to hear about that.
I'd be interested in hearing what he has to say.
You can read about it here.
Mr. Sakata's exhibit number 15.
It's titled “I Spent Time Talking About Memories.
I look forward to hearing from you.
I'm sorry. My name is Miku Kanamura, from Hyugaizaka 46.
I'm Sakata Tsuruka. Pleased to meet you.
Today, we have some very large paintings.
How many large paintings are on display today? There are 12 today.
One is about 3.5 meters long.
The total length is about 40 meters.
I see.
These are written on cloth.
Yes, it's written on gauze and touched.
That's amazing.
Is it okay? Wow!
It's actually made of this really soft gauze fabric.
And it's coated with boiled leather.
And then I put a coating on top to protect it from the rain.
on top to protect it from rain.
Like a waterproof finish.
That's right.
It was more like a curtain, so I was worried that it would become limp.
That's true. We made many prototypes, and sometimes we made a lot of mistakes.
It's hard work to redo things.
That's amazing!
It looks like a drawer!
Wow!
It's really much bigger than I thought it would be, about the size of a blackboard.
It's definitely a blackboard.
Maybe it's bigger than a blackboard.
It is indeed a blackboard. That picture is a picture of a blackboard.
It's true.
I've been talking and interviewing people in this town for months.
I've been working with the people of Hagiwara-cho's Kiyomichi district for about six months now, and I've been able to meet with them about once a month.
From small children to the elderly.
Talking about memories.
What kind of things they used to talk about on their way to school.
What they used to talk about on their way to school
We make pictures of these things.
I see.
I make pictures of the things we used to talk about.
I don't have any. I work with people in the city.
I'm sure it's filled with memories of all kinds of people.
It's a work of art that makes me happy.
It's so cute!
Thank you very much.
I was really inspired by your work.
Thank you for the wonderful time.
Thank you for a wonderful time.
It's not often that I get to talk to the creator of a piece of artwork.
I had a great time.
We came to a place called “Aroma House”.
There are some works by Aguri, who is a painter, and some works by Toru Nakazaki.
and one by Mr. Toru Nakazaki.
It's so old-fashioned!
It's like a good old house.
It looks like an old private house.
I wonder if it's cherry blossoms...
Cherry blossoms?
I'm surprised when I see it for the first time.
Look at this.
Open up!
Wow, it's like grandma's house.
It's amazing. It's like you have to go through something to make it seem real.
It's like you have to walk through it to get to the real world.
It's nice. It's interesting.
This is Yoro Hyotan Studio, where you can paint gourds.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
What kind of plant is this gourd?
Chestnut.
Chestnuts?
It looks like this.
I thought they were baked.
I'll take this one then.
How much do you need?
But...
Wow! The colors are quite strong.
It's already acrylic paint.
It's acrylic paint.
It's acrylic paint, so it goes on and on and on.
I have no hesitation.
It's all a matter of which side to put in front.
And...
Well...
There are some bumps on this side.
Shall we put it on this side?
It's done, but there's a little bump over here, so let's put it on this side.
It's done!
The only one in the world was made on a gourd!
Thank you very much.
Completed
The next day
When you are hungry, scoop your stomach When you are hungry, scoop your stomach When you are hungry, open your stomach When you are hungry, open your stomach When you are hungry, open your stomach When you are hungry, open your stomach When you are hungry, open your stomach When you are hungry, open your stomach When you are hungry, open your stomach
When you are hungry, open your stomach
Ah! Here it comes!
That's the one I was looking at!
If you don't like bugs, this is not the place for you.
If you don't like bugs, be careful!
Hello!
This looks like a praying mantis.
It looks like a praying mantis.
That's amazing.
That's why we're here today.
That's why I came to Nampei.
Actually...
There is a man
here.
works at this art festival.
Um...
I was kind of invited.
I had a chance to meet him.
So you're here.
Instructor Ohari.
Hello.
Hello, it's been a while.
It's been a while.
Yes, ma'am.
If you have. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
How are you doing? Have you seen Hinatazaka lately?
I'm looking.
I'm glad.
I'm sure everyone will be happy to see this.
I've come to Gifu to see you on your behalf.
I grew up being angry with my instructor.
I was still in junior high back then, right?
That's right.
In the blink of an eye.
In the blink of an eye, I became an adult woman.
In the blink of an eye, I was an adult.
It all happened so fast.
It's amazing.
I'm glad to see you're doing well.
Hey.
You, too.
Welcome back.
It's true, I feel a demon's empathy when I talk to you.
“Demon empathy.
That's the name you gave me.
You're the only one who's said it.
No, back then...
You supported us back then.
Maybe not everyone.
You know, the women...
It wasn't like this at all.
It's so much better now.
I have this environment, but I'm at peace.
of that time, of that era.
I think I'll go see one more thing.
I'm going to show you one more thing.
I'm going to show you something.
Ta-da!
It's a very bold piece of work.
It's quite a bold piece of work.
Wow, mushrooms are growing.
Mushrooms are growing like this!
Amazing!
That's the end of my trip to Gifu Prefecture, I've been exposed to so many different kinds of art today, and I'm really looking forward to seeing more.
As a person who is studying such things
As a student of art, I feel that I have to do my best.
I also felt that I should do my best
I also feel that I should do my best in my idol activities.
I also felt that I would like to make use of this kind of artwork in my idol activities.
I hope I can make the most of it.
That's all for now.
This is Kanamura.
Subscribe to my channel and click the Good button
Thank you very much!
See you soon!